Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 19ND-A-410
  - Series III
    - Restricted grades and reports
      - 1956, Senior Electives (Box 224, Folder 224 158)
      - 1956, Student Evaluations (Box 224, Folder 159-160)
      - Canadian Nurses' Association (Box 224, Folder 161)
      - 1957, Grades (Box 224, Folder 162)
      - 1957, Miscellaneous (Box 224, Folder 163)
      - 1957, Evaluation of Elective Experience (Box 224, Folder 164)
      - 1957, Elective Experience Requests, Aug 15th and Sep 15th (Box 224, Folder 165)
      - 1958, Miscellaneous (Box 225, Folder 166)
      - 1958, Grades (Box 225, Folder 167)
      - 1958, Cumulative Reports (Box 225, Folder 168)
      - 1958, Senior Conferences (Box 225, Folder 169)
      - 1958, Correspondence, re Experience (Box 225, Folder 170)
      - 1958, Evaluation of Elective Experience (Box 225, Folder 171)
    - Rumford Press Cuts from basic program (Box 226–227)
  - Series IV
    - Study of Students Enrolled at YSN by Pittsburgh U. School of Nursing -1959 (Box 228, Folder 1-2)
    - Selected List of YSN Grads. (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - YSN Integration of Psychiatric Nursing in the Basic Curriculum, Oct. 1948 (two black bound volumes) (Box 228, Folder 4-5)
    - Clinical and Field Work Experience, Correspondence, Ment. Health and Psych Nrs. Prg. 1952-59 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - "A Time Study of Nursing Activity in Rooming-In" (two unbound copies) (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Study by Mr. E.C.Hughes (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Outdated Descriptions -YSN -MHPN (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - Member, Committee on Future of Public Health at Yale (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Mental Health and Psych. Nursing Program -Field Work Opportunities, 1954-59 (Box 229, Folder 12)
    - Traineeship Grants prior to 1958 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Broadcasts E.J.Taylor and others (Box 229, Folder 14)
    - Cost Analysis for Collegiate Programs in Nursing Part II, NLN 1957 (Ringbound) (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - Cost Analysis for Collegiate Programs in Nursing Part I, NLN 1956 (Ringhound) (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Council -Graduate Program, 1955-59 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Council, 1959-60 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Council, 1961-62-63 (Box 230, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Council, 1960-61 (Box 230, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Council 1962-63 (Dean's Office) (Box 230, Folder 21)
    - Post Master's Teaching Committee, 1963-64 (Box 230, Folder 22)
    - YSN -Grace Nursing Staff Joint Committee (Box 230, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Travel 1963-64, and Professional Meetings (Box 230, Folder 24)
    - Graduate Schools, Schedules, 1963-64-65 (Box 230, Folder 25)
    - Master's Reports, 1960-61-62-63-64 (Box 230, Folder 26)
    - Outside Request for Research by YSN Faculty and Students 1963-65 (Box 230, Folder 27)
    - Editorial Consultation 1963-65 (Box 230, Folder 28)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Experience, 1963-64 (Box 230, Folder 29)
    - Admissions Committee, 1963-64 (Box 230, Folder 30)
    - Ad Hoc Criteria for Admissions Comm., 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 31)
    - Film Committee (Wald) 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 32)
    - Recording Devices, 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 33)
    - Ad Hoc Committee in Clinical Practive for Faculty, 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 34)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Public Health Nursing, 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 35)
    - Faculty Council (Dean's Office), 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 36)
    - Faculty Research Symposium, 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 37)
    - Post Masters Intern Committee, 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 38)
    - Measurements Workshop 101 (logic) and Nursing Practice Theory (Box 231, Folder 39)
    - Major: Public Health Nursing (Box 231, Folder 40)
    - Major: Maternal and Newborn Health Nursing (Box 231, Folder 41)
    - Major: Mental Health and Psychiatric Nursing (Box 231, Folder 42)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Seminar, 1963-64 (Box 231, Folder 43)
    - Faculty Research Symposium (extra copies), 1962, 1963, 1964 (Box 232, Folder 44)
    - Nursing Problems in Need of Research (Box 232, Folder 45)
    - Preparation for Parenthood Program (Prep. Childbirth Progr.) 1963-64 (Box 232, Folder 46)
    - Preparation for Parenthood Program (Prep. Childbirth Progr.) 1962-63 (Box 232, Folder 47)
    - Seminar in Administration (Box 232, Folder 48)
    - Alumnae College, 1963-64 (Box 232, Folder 49)
    - Research Methods Seminar II N204 a (Box 232, Folder 50)
    - Sociqlogy 105a, 1963-64 (Box 232, Folder 51)
    - Nursing 230 - Maternal, Newborn Health Nursing Seminar, 1964-65 (Box 232, Folder 52)
    - Education Seminar, 1963-64 (Box 232, Folder 53)
    - Logic-15B (Box 232, Folder 54)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 232, Folder 56)
    - Sybil Bellos Lectureship, 1963-64 (Box 232, Folder 57)
    - Boston University, 1962-64 (Box 232, Folder 58)
    - Bursar, Graduate Program, 1960-65 (Box 232, Folder 59)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1962-64 (Box 233, Folder 60)
    - Civil Defense Nursing, Conn. Council, 1964 (Box 233, Folder 61)
    - Columbia University (Box 233, Folder 62)
    - Commencement, 1963-64 (Box 233, Folder 63)
    - Conn. Assoc. for Mental Health, Prof. Advisory Comm., 1963-64 (Box 233, Folder 64)
    - Conn. Assoc. for Mental Health, Prof. Advisory Comm., 1963-64 (Box 233, Folder 65)
    - Conn. State Nurses Association, 1960- (Box 233, Folder 66)
    - Conn. State Dept. for Mental Health, 1963-64 (Box 233, Folder 67)
    - Conn. Public Health Nursing Agencies, (Board Members Organization), 1963 (Box 233, Folder 68)
    - Conn. State Department of Health, 1960-64 (Box 233, Folder 69)
    - Conn. State Board of Examiners for Nurses (Box 233, Folder 70)
    - District Nursing Association, Mt. Kisko, 1964 (Box 233, Folder 71)
    - Franklin S. DuBois Psychiatric Day Treatment Center, 1964 (Box 233, Folder 72)
    - Fellowships: Re information and Policies, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 73)
    - Annie W. Goodrich Professorship (Visiting Professors) (Box 234, Folder 77)
    - Hospitals, Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 234, Folder 78)
    - Interschool Committee on Foreign Students, 1964-65 (Box 234, Folder 79)
    - Institute for the Special Care of Newborn and premature Infants, Yale-N.H., 1963 (Box 234, Folder 80)
    - Institute of Living, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 81)
    - Insurance (Box 234, Folder 82)
    - Johns Hopkins Hospital (Box 234, Folder 83)
    - USPHS Student Loan Program, 1964-65 (Box 234, Folder 85)
    - M- Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1963-64 (Box 234, Folder 87)
    - Maternity Center Assoc. New York City, 1947-65 (Box 234, Folder 88)
    - Medical Board - G - NHCH, 1953-61 (Box 234, Folder 89)
    - Legislation, Re: Nursing, 1964 (Box 235, Folder 90)
    - National Defense Education Act, 1962-63 (Box 235, Folder 91)
    - Council of Member Agencies, DBHDP, Nov.16-18, 1966, Seattle (Box 235, Folder 93)
    - NLN - General, 1961-64 (National League for Nurses) (Box 235, Folder 94)
    - NLN Council on Research in Nursing, 19Q4- (Box 235, Folder 95)
    - NLN Accrediting Service 1963 (Box 235, Folder 96)
    - NLN Dept. of Baccalaureate and Higher Degrees, Spring (Box 235, Folder 97)
    - NLN - Dept. of Bacc. and Higher Degree Programs, Council of (Box 235, Folder 98)
    - New England Board of Higher Education, 1964- (Box 236, Folder 99)
    - New England Board of Higher Education, 1963-64 (Box 236, Folder 100)
    - NEBHE -Comm. for Regional Planning for Short Term Courses in New England, 1960-64 (Box 236, Folder 101)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse~Association, 1958-64 (Box 236, Folder 102)
    - New England Regional Conf. on Public Health Nursing Education, Inc., 1959-1964 (Box 236, Folder 103)
    - Norris, K. -1956 (Box 236, Folder 104)
    - Nursing Outlook (Formerly the Public Health Nurse), 1953-64 (Box 236, Folder 105)
    - Nursing Research, 1953-64 (Box 236, Folder 106)
    - Patient Population in Nursing Nomes in South Central Conn., Proj. of Dept. of EPH, 1964 (Box 236, Folder 107)
    - Peace Corps, 1963-64 (Box 236, Folder 108)
    - Policies and Procedures Research (Grants), 1961-64 (Box 237, Folder 111)
    - Publicity -YSN Brocures and Posters, 1960-64 (Box 237, Folder 112)
    - Questionnaires, 1959-63 (Box 237, Folder 113)
    - Questionnaire and Inquiries, 1964-65 (Box 237, Folder 114)
    - Questionnaire to Grad. Students, 1959-63, 1964 (Box 237, Folder 115)
    - Recruitment of College Gra~uates into Nursing, 1964-65 (Box 237, Folder 116)
    - University of Rhode Island, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 117)
    - Scholarships for Graduate Students, 1955-64 (Box 238, Folder 119-120)
    - Syracuse University, 1960-63 (Box 238, Folder 121)
    - S -Miscellaneous, 1963-64 (Box 238, Folder 122)
    - Fulbright Awards -Office of the Provost, 1952-64 (Box 238, Folder 123)
    - Tests and Testing, Services, 1964 (Box 238, Folder 124)
    - Tuition Fees, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 125)
    - U.S. Army Nurse Corps, 1964 (Box 238, Folder 126)
    - USPHS, Patent Policy, 1964 (United States Public Health Service) (Box 238, Folder 127)
    - Professional Nurse Traineeship Program, NT-36-C7, IBM No.92-49-0002), 1963-64 (Box 238, Folder 128)
    - Professional Nurse Traineeship Program (NT-36-C6), 1963 (Box 238, Folder 129)
    - USPHS Research and Study Grants Available -.Misc.,1956-63 (Box 238, Folder 130)
    - Professional Nurse Traineeship Program, Refer to: UN ~NT-36-C5 (Box 239, Folder 131)
    - USPHS Children's Bureau, 1962-65 (Box 239, Folder 132)
    - USPHS -Misc., 1947-64 (Box 239, Folder 133)
    - University of Texas andTulane U., U. of Tennessee, 1961-65 (Box 239, Folder 134)
    - Universities, L-Z Misc., 1960-64 (Box 239, Folder 135)
    - Wiley Publishers, The John Wiley and Son, Inc., 1964 (Box 239, Folder 136)
    - V.A.Hospital, West Haven, Research Arrangements, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 137)
    - World Health Organization, 1964 (Box 239, Folder 138)
    - Yale -Acknowledgments of gifts (Box 239, Folder 139)
    - Yale Advisory Comm. on Development of Yale-New Haven Med. Center, 1964 (Box 239, Folder 140)
    - YSN Alumnae Assoc. -Visits to Regional Groups, 1964- (Box 239, Folder 141)
    - Yale Press: Mr. Weaver (Box 239, Folder 142)
    - Yale School of Nursing: Lecture Series, 1963-64 (Box 239, Folder 143)
    - Yale: Sterling Dormitory (Box 239, Folder 144)
    - Yale: Agreement between YSN -Yale New Haven Hospital, 1952-63 (Box 239, Folder 145)
    - Amer. Medical Association, 1961-64 (Box 239, Folder 146)
    - Amer. Nurses Association, General, 1964 (Box 239, Folder 147)
    - ANA Biennial Convention, June 15-19, 1964, Atlantic City (Box 239, Folder 148)
    - ANA Definition of Psychiatric Nursing Practice, 1964 (Box 240, Folder 149)
    - Amer. Nurses Foundation, 1961-64 (Box 240, Folder 150)
    - D. Appleton and Company, Inc., Book Publishers, 1964 (Box 240, Folder 151)
    - Audio-Visual Aids (Box 240, Folder 152)
    - Methods of Research, N 200 (Box 240, Folder 153)
    - Nursing 203, Research Seminar (Box 240, Folder 154)
    - Clinical Practice in Psychiatric Nursing (Box 240, Folder 155)
    - Public Health Major, 1954-1965 (Box 240, Folder 156)
    - Introduction to Statistics, N20lb (Box 240, Folder 157)
    - Course Advisors, 1964-65 (Box 240, Folder 158)
    - Ad Hoc Criteria for Masters Report Committee, 1963-64 (Box 240, Folder 159)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Conn. Nursing Needs, 1964 (Box 240, Folder 160)
    - Clinical and Research Instruction Coordination, 1964 (Box 240, Folder 161)
    - Committee on Ethics for Publication, 1964-65 (Box 240, Folder 162)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Masters Report Criteria, (Wald) (Box 240, Folder 163)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Practice (Wald) (Box 240, Folder 164)
    - Dean's Meetings, 1963-64 (Box 240, Folder 165)
    - Review Committee ~ Faculty Research, 1964-65 (Box 240, Folder 166)
    - Yale New Haven Medical Center -Misc. (Box 240, Folder 167)
    - Yale New Haven Medical Center (Box 241, Folder 168)
    - Yale Alumni Board, 1949-64 (Box 241, Folder 169)
    - Yale Miscellaneous, 1960-66 (Box 241, Folder 170)
    - Faculty Personnel Policies, 1957-65 (Box 241, Folder 171)
    - Helen Hadley Hall, Yale U., 1961-64 photographs (Box 241, Folder 172)
    - Housing -Yale (Box 241, Folder 173)
    - Yale Medical Librarian, Kilgour, 1960-64 (Box 241, Folder 174)
    - Maintenance Dept., 1960-64 (Box 241, Folder 175)
    - Yale News Bureau, 1927-64 photograph (Box 241, Folder 176)
    - Pres. Kingman Brewster, Jr., 1963-64 (Box 241, Folder 177)
    - Yale Provost, Charles Taylor, 1963-64 (Box 242, Folder 178)
    - Yale Study Skills Office: Academic Writing Course 1958-64 (Box 242, Folder 179)
    - Yale Treasurer's Office, Mr. Roberts, 1955-65 (Box 242, Folder 180)
    - YSN -Nursing Lecture-:,Series, 1964-65 (Box 242, Folder 181)
    - YSN -Nursing Lecture Series, 1963-64 (Box 242, Folder 182)
    - YSN -General, 1960-64 (Box 242, Folder 183)
    - YSN -Space Needs, 1963-64 (Box 242, Folder 184)
    - Review of the Daily Nursing Reports, 1953-63 (Grace N.H. Hospital) (blue folder) (Box 242, Folder 185)
    - Facts and Figures 1953-63 (Grace N.H. Hospital) (Box 242, Folder 186)
    - Fiancial Aid to Canadian Students, 1962-64 (Box 242, Folder 187)
    - Books and Reprints on Order for YSN, 1963-65 (Box 242, Folder 188)
    - On-Going Research Corresp., 1964 (Box 242, Folder 189)
    - Current Research, 1964 (Box 242, Folder 190)
    - USPHS -On-Going Research, Corresp. 1963 (Box 243, Folder 191)
    - On-Going Research Material, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 192)
    - USPHS -On-Going Research -Corresp., 1961-62 (Box 243, Folder 193)
    - On-Going Research, Lists, Addresses, etc., 1959-63 (Box 243, Folder 194)
    - USPHS -On-Going Research -Terminated Reports, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 195)
    - Terminated Reports -Corresp., 1964 (Box 243, Folder 196)
  - Historical Material, Series V
    - Letters from Annie W. Goodrich to her secretary M.L.Carpenter -some personal, some during Deanship, some after retirement (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Clippings on Miss Taylor's appointment as Professor of Psychiatric Nursing (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Reports and excerpt from speeches by Dean Winternitz, M.D. (missing) (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Comm. on Historical Source Materials in Nursing -CLN. (1957-63) (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Historical -Time Study, Bulletin 1 and 2, 1928 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Special folder: Macmillan Co. re: books about A.W.Goodrich (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Dean Goodrich's trip to Japan (1930) (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - Material re: Annie Goodrich Memorial Service at Dwight Memorial Chapel, 1955 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - YSN teaching methods -Addresses or articles by faculty members or others (1930-33) (Box 244, Folder 10-11)
    - Annie W. Goodrich -Miscellaneous Material indicating contacts with foreign countries (1920-30) (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - A.W.Goodrich -Personal Files (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Photographs re: A.W.G. (photographs) (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Exhibit -A.W.G. 80th Birthday (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Exhibit -A.W.G. 80th Birthday dinner -Waldorf (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - A.W.G. 80th Birthday dinner -Waldorf (Alumnae) (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - A.W.G. Personal -Trip to the Orient 1930 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - A.W.G. European Trip -1925 (incl. letters to and from YSN office) (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Students' papers Class of 1950 -re: Miss Goodrich (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - Student papers on AWG Exhibit -Class of 1948 (Box 245, Folder 21)
    - A.W.G.Miscellaneous Material indicating contributions to organizations other than Yale in the U.S. (Box 245, Folder 22)
    - A.W.G. -Personal -Los Angeles and San Francisco Trip 1932 (Box 246, Folder 23)
    - A.W.G. -Personal -Speaking Engagements etc. (Box 246, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous articles and reprints -Miss Taylor (Box 246, Folder 25)
    - Report of the President and Comm. of the Corporation on Educ. Policies, 1934, 1935, 1936 (Box 246, Folder 26)
    - Reprints of Miss Effie Taylor's speeches (Box 246, Folder 27)
    - Effie J. Taylor, Papers before 1930 (Box 246, Folder 28-29)
    - Effie J. Taylor, Papers and Pamphlets 1930-33 (Box 247, Folder 30-31)
    - Effie J. Taylor, Papers and Pamphlets 1934-44 (Box 247, Folder 32)
    - Effie J. Taylor, Papers -Dates undnown (Box 247, Folder 33-34)
    - E.J.T. -Miscellaneous (Box 247, Folder 35)
    - Yale School of Medicine -General Selected Items (Box 247, Folder 36)
    - Congratulatory Messages and Endowment, 1929 (Box 247, Folder 37)
    - Assn. Collegiate Schools ofNuraing, Early data (1936-" (Box 248, Folder 38)
    - Connecticut Training School -Mimeo. Brief History (Box 248, Folder 39)
    - I Remember When "A Collection of Memoirs of N.H. Hospital by past and present employees and associates (1938-45) " (Box 248, Folder 40)
    - Effie J. Taylor -Papers and pamphlets, July 1944 (Box 248, Folder 41)
    - E.J.T. -Exhibit Summer 1965 (Box 248, Folder 42)
    - Connecticut Training School -Miscel. Material (Box 248, Folder 43)
    - Connecticut Training School -Material of historical nature -general (photograph) (Box 248, Folder 44-45)
    - Faculty -Admin. Committee -1926 (Box 249, Folder 46)
    - Yale Univ. Secretary's office -correspondence 1923-26 (Box 249, Folder 47)
    - Annie W. Goodrich -Papers and pamph1ets, 1920-30 (Box 249, Folder 48-49)
    - YSN Historical Material 1936-59 (Box 249, Folder 50)
    - Misc. Material pertaining to Florence Nightingale (Box 249, Folder 51)
    - Tape recording -alumnae day, Feb. 21, 1959 (Box 249, Folder 53)
    - The Nursing Education Bulletin, Vol.II No.2, 1929-30, re: A. Nutting (Box 249, Folder 54)
    - YSN Bulletin No.3, 1931 (Box 249, Folder 55)
    - Early material relating to YSN (1920's) (Box 249, Folder 56)
    - Appointments, YSN Faculty and Staff -Correspondence (Box 250, Folder 57)
    - YSN -Minutes of early conferences 1923-24 (Box 250, Folder 58)
    - YSN Faculty or Admin. Corom. actions -Correspondence with Univ. Officials, 1925-30 (Box 250, Folder 59)
    - Faculty council-Meetings - Early Material (1923-27) (Box 250, Folder 60)
    - General Articles about the School (Box 250, Folder 61)
    - Reports of the President and Dean of Medical School Statements of other Univ. and/or Hospital Officials (Box 250, Folder 62)
    - Angell, James Rowland (President) July 1934 -(1935-37) (Box 250, Folder 63)
    - Angell, James Rowland (President) 1923 -June 1934 (Box 250, Folder 64)
    - Provost --Dean Graves -Early Material re: staff appointments and salaries (1923-27) (Box 250, Folder 65)
    - Provost -Dean Graves -Early Material re: Student and School Problems (Box 250, Folder 66)
    - Rappelye, Dr. W.C. -Early material relating to affili~tions with other schools (Box 250, Folder 67)
    - Rappelye, Dr. W.C. -Early material relative to students in YSN (Box 251, Folder 68)
    - Rappelye, Dr. W.C. - Miscellaneous correspondence (1924-25) (Box 251, Folder 69)
    - Bursar - Early correspondence (Box 251, Folder 70)
    - Memoranda - General 1924-25 (Box 251, Folder 72)
    - Library Committee Minutes and Reports (1924-27) (Box 251, Folder 73)
    - A.W.Buck - General Correspondence (1928-33) (Box 251, Folder 74)
    - Brown University - 1925 (Box 251, Folder 75)
    - A.W.Goodrich Personal re: Lillian Clayton (Box 251, Folder 76)
    - Army School of Nursing - A.W.G. Personal 1921-26 (Box 251, Folder 77)
    - Henry Street Settlement (incl. Lillian Wald) 1923-24 (Box 251, Folder 78)
    - Misc. letters from individuals, re: A.W.G. (Box 251, Folder 79)
    - A.W.G. Papers, articles 1927-52 (Box 251, Folder 80)
    - A.W.G. Misc. Data (Box 252, Folder 81)
    - Establishment of YSN - Articles concerning, editorials, etc. (Box 252, Folder 82)
    - YSN Historical Material - Printed Agreements, other printed material (Box 252, Folder 83)
    - YSN Historical Material - Copies of Agreements, Descriptions of the School (Box 252, Folder 84)
    - YSN Historical - Conferences on Establ. and Organization of School, 1923-26 (Box 252, Folder 85)
    - A.W. Buck - re: Staff Appointments (1926-3Q). (Box 252, Folder 86)
    - YSN Budgets and Gen. Financial 1929-31 (Box 252, Folder 87)
    - YSN Budgets and Gen. Financial (1929-32) (Box 253, Folder 88)
    - YSN Budgets and General Financial (1926-29) (Box 253, Folder 89)
    - YSN Budgets and Gen. Financial (1923-26) (Box 253, Folder 90)
    - Budget - General (1924-31) (Box 253, Folder 91)
    - Nathan Smith Hall - Early Material - Reports by Norma SeIbert (1925-27) photographs (Box 253, Folder 92)
    - Nathan Smith Hall House Comm. Minutes of Meetings (1924-25) (Box 253, Folder 93)
    - Equipment or Bureau of Purchases"- Nathan Smith Hall (1923-25) (Box 253, Folder 94)
    - YSN Commencement
      - 1933 (Box 253, Folder 95)
      - 1932 (Box 253, Folder 96)
      - 1931 (Box 253, Folder 97)
      - 1930 (Box 253, Folder 98)
      - 1929 (Box 253, Folder 99)
      - 1928 (Box 253, Folder 100)
      - 1927 (Box 253, Folder 101)
      - 1926 (Box 253, Folder 102)
    - Equipment of Bureau of Purchases YSN (Box 253, Folder 103)
    - Forms 1933-35 (Box 254, Folder 104)
    - Forms Samples, in use, 1927-32 (Box 254, Folder 105)
    - Forms - Samples (Box 254, Folder 106)
    - Uniforms - early material, mainly gingham uniform dresses (Box 254, Folder 111)
    - Uniforms - early material mainly re coats and hats (Box 254, Folder 112)
    - Uniforms - early material mainly re collars and cuffs (Box 254, Folder 113)
    - Yale University Dept. of Health (1924-25) (Box 254, Folder 114)
    - Treasurer's Office majnly re Nathan Smith Hall (1925-26) (Box 255, Folder 115)
    - Treasurer's Office - mainly re salaries and budget (1924-26) (Box 255, Folder 116)
    - Treasurer's Office - mainly re. student matters (1924-27) (Box 255, Folder 117)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Assoc. historical before 1959 (Box 255, Folder 118)
    - VNA Hew Haven (1924-26) (Box 255, Folder 119)
    - Search of historical materials for Dean Wald (1966) (Box 255, Folder 120)
    - Hospital Staff members (items concerning member without faculty appt.) (1946) (Box 255, Folder 121)
    - Dean's Search Committee (1966) (Box 255, Folder 122)
    - Basic Program Closing - Historical Material (1956-57) (Box 255, Folder 123)
    - Historical maps displaying locations of Grads (1926-58) world map showing where grads have served (Box 255, Folder 124)
    - Articles by YSN Grads, faculty, students (Box 255, Folder 125)
    - Opportunities for Nursing Education in Connecticut Reprint (Box 256, Folder 126)
    - Alumnae News 1946 (Box 256, Folder 127)
    - Engagement Calendar 1946 (A Birthday Tribute to A.W.G.) YUSNAA (Box 256, Folder 128)
    - White Task Force Story of the Nurse Corps, USN. Prep. by two YSN grads (Box 256, Folder 129)
    - Misc. material honoring A.W.G. and Alumnae Assoc. letters and photos (Box 256, Folder 131)
    - 75th Anniversary of Nursing Banquet, ANAt Biltmore, NY Nov 1948 (photo only) (Box 256, Folder 132)
    - Historical Sketch of the ANA -reprint 1929 (Box 256, Folder 134)
    - 35th Annual Report of the YSN-1929 (Box 256, Folder 135)
    - YSN -Alumnae Assoc. Guest Book (1947-57) (Box 256, Folder 136)
    - 25th Anniv. Exercises of YSN, 1949 (Box 256, Folder 137)
    - Box of printing dies and slides re. infectious disease symptoms (Box 257, Folder 138)
    - Annie W. Goodrich Memorial Service (Box 257, Folder 139)
    - Bulletin of YSN 1933-34 (Box 257, Folder 140)
    - Amer. Jrn. of Nrsg., July 1934, Vo1.34 No.7 with article, re AWG) (Box 257, Folder 141)
    - Exhibit Identification Cards, re. A.W.G. (Box 257, Folder 142)
    - TheA.W.G. Post-Grad. Psychiatric Nurses Assoc. Neuro-Psych. Institute, Hartford, 1939 (Box 257, Folder 143)
    - The Story of the Amer. Jrn. of Nursing -1946 (Box 257, Folder 144)
    - The Nursing Education Bulletin-February 1940 (Box 257, Folder 145)
    - Historical Sketch of the ANA, 1929 (Box 257, Folder 146)